ANTHONY MARSHALL

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- 027 658 4855
- anthonymarshall@gmail.com
- Auckland, New Zealand
- https://anthonymarshall.io

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Applied Science (Software Engineering)

Auckland University of Technology

University Entrance

Sacred Heart College, Auckland

CERTIFICATIONS

Microsoft Data Analyst Associate 2021



SKILLS

- .Net
- Java
- Sql Server
- MySql
- Postgresql
- Elasticsearch
- HTML/CSS/JS/React
- Power BI
- Palantir
- Sharepoint
- Git
- CI/CD
- Clean Architecture (SOLID)

PROFILE

I'm a software developer who has 10+ years of commercial experience building web desktop, mobile and server based systems for a wide variety of industries, such as government, utilities, finance, marketing/advertising, retail and real estate.

Checkout my portfolio site for more details. anthonymarshall.io

EXPERIENCE

L3 Software Engineer

New Zealand Government (NZIC) | Auckland | 2017 - PRESENT

Currently working as a senior engineer for a government agency within the NZ Intelligence Community. Please contact me for more details.

This role focuses on building and maintaining the data integrations, APIs and applications for the business's Data Analytics platforms and COTS systems.

Key technologies used in this role: Java, Palantir, Elasticsearch, .Net, Sharepoint and Power BI, GltLab, Jenkins

Full Stack Developer

DATACOM | Auckland | 2017

Assigned primarily to Datacom's client, Barfoot & Thompson.

Key achievement was being the lead developer on Barfoot's SalesKit project from conception to release. This is an application used by sales agents to create and design professionally printed promotional material and property listing documentation. This product has proven to be highly successful to Barfoot & Thompson, and is actively used by the business today.

Key technologies used in this role: React, Redux, .Net, Sql Server

Technical Lead

BBD Perfect Storm | London | 2012 - 2017

Advertising agency in London. Key responsibilities were to develop web, desktop and mobile applications to support brand campaigns, and to manage the development team (4 devs plus contractors), define development processes and be the technical contact for clients.

Key technologies used in this role: C#, Asp.net, WPF, Sql Server, Episerver, PHP, Laravel, Magento, MySql, Postgres, HTML/CSS/JS, SASS, Angular 1 & 2, React, Git, AWS, Jenkins

INTERESTS

Tennis, Chess, Travel, Hiking, Running, DIY, Programming

REFERENCES

Available on request

EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

Senior Analyst Programmer

Aimia Ltd | Auckland | 2007-2011

AIMIA (formerly Carlson Marketing Ltd) are a leading provider of customer loyalty programmes. For their credit card systems, I helped build the loyalty points calculation engines (processing 100,000+ credit card transactions per day) and developed the e-commerce points redemption websites for clients such as Vodafone, Westpac, ASB, ANZ and Pfizer.

Systems that I have worked on include:

www.hotpoints.co.nz – Westpac bank's customer loyalty points programme www.truerewards.co.nz – ASB bank's customer loyalty points programme

Key technologies used in this role: ASP.Net, C#, SQL Server, SQL DTS and SSIS, Crystal, Kentico CMS

Analyst Programmer

Kinetiq Ltd | Auckland | 2005 - 2007

Kinetiq Ltd is a provider of web and desktop based data management solutions for the international energy market. In this role I helped build energy-usage monitoring and billing management systems.

Key technologies used in this role: ASP.Net, C#.Net, SQL Server and Oracle 10g

Software Developer

Blueday Ltd | Auckland | 2004 - 2005

This was my first full-time position as an IT professional after completing my university degree. I specialised in web development for small to medium sized businesses.

Key technologies used in this role: Classic ASP, ASP.net and SQL Server.